http://www.lawsonsp.com/technical-support/customer-service/terms-a-conditions

EquipmentScreen Printing Start Up EquipmentCustom PackagesHobbyScoutScout XLBeginnerIntermediateAdvancedProfessionalMini-MaxMini-TrooperFace MaskFinancingTextile EquipmentManual PressesAutomatic PressesConveyor DryersFlash UnitsPlaten ChoicesAthletic NumberingUsed EquipmentPre-Press & AuxiliaryExposure UnitsCTS MachinesScreen CleaningScreen CoatingScreen DryingHigh-Pressure WashersDrying RacksFrames & AccessoriesSqueegees & FloodbarsShop EquipmentHeat Transfer EquipmentDigital EquipmentDirect-To-GarmentDTG PrintersDTG Pretreat MachinesHybrid DTG PrintersDigital & Ink Jet DryersComputer-To-ScreenEpson Inkjet PrintersLaser PrintersSoftwareRoland Printers/Cutters & PlottersGraphic EquipmentPressesDryersSuppliesTrainingClassesScreen Printing ClassArtwork ClassDark Garment ClassAutomatic Screen Printing ClassDigital/SublimationEpson DTG Training ClassClass ScheduleWhere to StaySt. Louis HotelsAtlanta HotelsTraining/Tutorials VideosLawson TVSupportHow to Start a Screen Printing BusinessHow T-Shirts Are PrintedPrint SupportPlastisol Textile InkEpson InkSDS/MSD SheetsEquipment Support TicketDigital/Software SupportTechnical Support FAQSupport ArticlesCustomer ServiceCustomer Service FAQLawson FormsPayment TermsGuaranteeTerms & ConditionsNon-ProfitIndustry LinksService LocationsFinancingAboutAbout UsMeet Our TeamEvent ListingsTestimonialsEmploymentBlogLawson UpdatesEquipment & SuppliesEducation & TrainingContactOffices & DealersContact UsJoin Our Mailing List
Screen Printing Equipment > Support > Customer Service > Terms & Conditions
Customer Service - Terms & Conditions
The information contained in our catalogs and on our web site is based on various tests and experience performed by the manufacture's whom we represent. However, conditions may vary from shop to shop and the suggestions given must be considered as recommendations only with no warranties expressed or implied. It is the printer's responsibility to pretest the ink and all other items used prior to production. The seller assumes no responsibility for results obtained or damages incurred from their used by the buyer in whole or in part.
All orders are subject to acceptance by Lawson Screen Products, Inc. No oral agreements, guarantees, promises, representations or warranties other than those stated in writing will be binding. Lawson will not be liable for any consequential damages incurred for any reason.
Lawson's Terms and Conditions of Quotation, Acceptance and Sale shall prevail. Purchaser is liable for all legal fees and collection costs if this account is placed for collections. A monthly service charge of one and one-half percent (1.5%) will be charged for delinquent accounts.
Lawson Screen & Digital Products, Inc. Terms of Use Web-Site Policy
These Terms of Use govern your use and access to this website.
Lawson may change, update, delete or add to these terms of use over time. By accessing and using this website, you agree to these Terms of Use, all policies within this website, and all changes or modifications to the foregoing. If you do not agree to these Terms of Use, such policies, or any modifications thereto, please do not use this website.
Lawson Privacy Policy Statement
Lawson encourages you to read Lawson's Privacy Policy Statement so that you may make an informed decision about using this website.
Copyright
All copyrighted and copyrightable materials on this website, including, without limitation, the design, text, artwork, technical documentation, manuals, diagrams, product information, graphics, images, pictures, photographs, sound files and other files ("Materials"), and the selection and arrangement thereof, are owned by Lawson and/or its licensors. No Materials may be copied, imitated or used in any way whatsoever without the prior written permission of Lawson except that Lawson grants to you limited rights to access the website and use the Materials for personal, non-commercial and informational use only provided that the Lawson copyright notice is reproduced therein. This license may not be sub-licensed, assigned or transferred in any manner.
The foregoing license grant does NOT include the right for you to: publish, publicly perform or display, or distribute to any third party any Materials, including reproduction on any computer network or broadcast or publications media; market, sell or make commercial use of this site or any Materials; systematically collect and use of any data or content including the use of any data spiders, robots, or similar data gathering, mining or extraction methods; make derivative uses of this site or the Materials; or use, frame or utilize framing techniques to enclose any portion of this site (including the images found at this site or any text or the layout/design of any page or form contained on a page). Except for the limited license granted to you, you are not conveyed any other right or license by implication, estoppel, or otherwise in or under any patent, trademark, copyright, or proprietary right of Lawson or any third party. Any unauthorized use of this Web Site will terminate the permission or license granted by these Terms of Use and may violate applicable law including copyright laws, trademark laws (including trade dress), and communications regulations and statutes.
Trademarks
"Lawson, Lawson Screen Products, Lawson Screen & Digital Products" and the Lawson logo, and any proprietary product or service names contained in this website are either trademarks or registered trademarks of Lawson or its licensors, and may not be copied, imitated or used, in whole or in part, without the prior written permission of Lawson. In addition, all page headers, custom graphics, button icons and scripts are service marks, trademarks and/or trade dress of Lawson and may not be copied, imitated or used, in whole or in part, without the prior written permission of Lawson. All other trademarks, registered trademarks, product names and company names or logos mentioned herein are the property of their respective owners.
Accounts and Passwords
You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account and password and for restricting access to your computer, and you agree to accept responsibility for all activities that occur under your account or password. Lawson reserves the right to refuse service, terminate accounts or cancel orders in its sole discretion.
Choice of Law and Jurisdiction
This website is controlled from the Lawson offices located in St. Louis, Missouri. Accordingly, the Terms shall be governed by the laws of the state of Missouri, without giving effect to its conflict of laws provisions. By accessing this website, you agree that any action at law or in equity arising out of or relating to the use of the website, including the purchase of any product, supplies or maintenance here from, shall be filed only in state or federal court located in St. Louis, Missouri and you hereby irrevocably and unconditionally consent and submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of such courts over any suit, action or proceeding arising.
General Provisions
Lawson reserves the right, without notice and in its sole discretion, to terminate your ability to use this website, and to block or prevent future access to and use of the website. If any provision of these Terms shall be deemed unlawful, void, or for any reason unenforceable, then that provision shall be deemed severable from these terms and conditions and shall not affect the validity and enforceability of any remaining provisions. These Terms, including any applicable policy contained in this site, constitute the entire agreement between you and Lawson relating to the subject matter addressed herein.
Disclaimers
This Website, Any Products/Goods, Services Or Software, And All Information and/or Content of the Web Site are Provided on an "As Is" Basis Without Warranties of Any Kind, Either Express or Implied, Including, Without Limitation, Implied Warranties Of Merchantability, Non-Infringment, or Fitness For a Particular Purpose.
The Information and/or content Contained in This Website Is Believed To Be Accurate as of the Date the Information and/or Content Was Added to this Website.
The Information and/or Content at this Website May Contain Typographical Errors, Inaccuracies, or Omissions. Lawson Reserves the Right yo Correct Any Errors, Inaccuracies or Omissions or Update Information and/or Content at any Time Without Prior Notice. Lawson Is Not Responsible For Typographical Errors or Omissions Relating to Pricing, Text or Photography.
Changes or Modifications
Lawson reserves the right to change or modify any of the terms and conditions contained in these Terms of Use or any policy of the website, at any time and in its sole discretion. If Lawson decides to change its Terms of Use or a policy, Lawson will post a new version on its website and update the date. Any changes or modification will be effective upon posting of the revisions. Your continued use of this website following the posting of the changes or modifications will constitute your acceptance of such changes or modifications. You should frequently review these Terms of Use (including its date) and applicable policies from time-to-time to understand the terms and conditions that apply to your use of the website.
Privacy Policy
The Information We Collect Lawson does not require visitors to supply personally identifiable information when accessing public areas of the site. When you browse the website, you do so anonymously, unless you have submitted an online registration form and selected a password. We do log your IP address (the Internet address of your computer) to give us an idea of which part of our website you visit and how long you spend there. But we do not link your IP address to any personal information unless you have logged into our website through registration and a password.
We do collect personally identifiable information when you register, access certain restricted site areas, place an order, request other information, or otherwise communicate with us about our offerings. Additionally, we may collect personally identifiable information when you register to attend a seminar, ask to be included in an email or other mailing list, submit an entry for a sweepstakes or other promotion, or you submit your personal information to Lawson for any other reason. From time to time, Lawson receives personal information from business partners and vendors. Lawson only uses such information if it has been collected in accordance with acceptable industry privacy practices consistent with this policy and applicable laws. Personally identifiable information may be merged with other information Lawson already knows, such as whether you are a current Lawson customer, or whether you or your organization has had past contact with Lawson sales or marketing activities.
How we use the Information Lawson collects this information for a variety of reasons, including Lawson's effort to inform you of product upgrades, special offers, and to ensure that you have access to information which is likely to be of interest to you. However, we do not sell or rent personally identifiable information to other organizations. On occasion, we may share personally identifiable information with an authorized Lawson dealer.
Your Choices You may request, at any time, that the personally identifiable information you provide on a registration page or when updating your profile not be used for direct e-mail marketing purposes by Lawson. The best way to do this is to opt-out of any e-blast you may receive, which is clearly stated at the bottom of the e-blast page. You will have the option to modify your e-mail subscriptions or to remove your name entirely from all Lawson direct e-mail marketing activities. If you do receive direct e-mail marketing communication from Lawson, you will also receive options to remove your name from future mailings directly on the e-mail. The processes described on the e-mail will be effective even if you are not a registered user of the website. If you need further help or have additional questions, please contact us.  Please provide your full name, e-mail address and phone number so that we may address your concerns appropriately.
Within the Lawson web site(s), there may be "links" to other non-Lawson web sites. It is also possible that non-Lawson web sites may link into Lawson web sites. We are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices employed by those non-Lawson web sites.
Cookies As is the case with many sites, when you visit our site or complete a registration form, we reserve the right to place a "cookie" on your computer, which helps us identify you more quickly when you return to use our web site. Our use of this technology does not mean that we automatically know anything about you. They are used to identify you as a unique visitor to the site. We will not use "cookies" or other devices to follow your click stream on the Internet,but will use them to determine which pages or information you find most useful or interesting at our own Web site(s).
Most browsers permit you to refuse to accept a "cookie" offered by a Web site. You will not be denied access to any part of our web site(s) because of your refusal to accept a "cookie," but your transactions through this Web site may be delayed due to the time it takes you to re-enter basic information necessary to complete a transaction.
Changes to the Privacy Policy Due to the rapidly evolving nature of technologies, Lawson may occasionally update this privacy statement. As a result, revisions and changes will simply be posted to this privacy statement web page.
Questions or Suggestions If you have any questions and would like to speak with someone at Lawson regarding this Policy, call David at 314-382-9300; or contact us.
Start-Up PackagesCustom PackagesHobbyScoutScout XLBeginnerIntermediateAdvancedProfessionalMini-MaxMini-TrooperFace Mask
Textile EquipmentManual PressesAutomatic PressesConveyor DryersFlash UnitsPlaten ChoicesAthletic Numbering
Pre-Press & AuxiliaryExposure UnitsCTS MachinesScreen CleaningScreen CoatingScreen DryingHigh-Pressure WashersDrying RacksFrames & AccessoriesSqueegees & FloodbarsShop Equipment
Digital Printing EquipmentDirect-To-GarmentDTG PrintersDTG Pretreat MachinesHybrid DTG PrintersDigital & Ink Jet DryersComputer-To-ScreenEpson Inkjet PrintersLaser PrintersSoftwareRoland Printers/Cutters & Plotters
Lawson TV
Customer Testimonial Channel
Direct-To-Garment Equipment Channel
Digital Printing Equipment Channel
Screen Printing Equipment Channel
Training/Tutorials Channel
Financing
Financing
Used Equipment
Email UsCall 314-382-93005110 Penrose St.St. Louis, MO 63115
Newsletter
Text PRINT to 833-689-0588 for exclusive deals & tips sent directly to your phone
EquipmentScreen Printing Start Up EquipmentFinancingTextile EquipmentUsed EquipmentPre-Press & AuxiliaryHeat Transfer EquipmentDigital EquipmentGraphic EquipmentSuppliesTrainingClassesClass ScheduleWhere to StayTraining/Tutorials VideosLawson TVSupportHow to Start a Screen Printing BusinessHow T-Shirts Are PrintedPrint SupportSDS/MSD SheetsEquipment Support TicketDigital/Software SupportTechnical Support FAQSupport ArticlesCustomer ServiceFinancingAboutAbout UsMeet Our TeamEvent ListingsTestimonialsEmploymentBlogLawson UpdatesEquipment & SuppliesEducation & TrainingContactOffices & DealersContact UsJoin Our Mailing List
